#### Contact

nash.radovanovich@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ nenadradovanovic (LinkedIn) nenad.xyz (Personal)

### Top Skills

React.js Node.js

JavaScript

### Languages

Spanish (Limited Working)
Bosnian (Native or Bilingual)
Serbian (Native or Bilingual)

#### Honors-Awards

Fonklame Case Study - First Place

# Nenad Radovanovic

Fullstack Web Developer (React / Node) | Belgrade

## Summary

Tech enthusiast. Moved abroad, joining startups in San Francisco, Stockholm, and Cyprus.

Extensive experience acquired while in the Valley with a strong insight into the startup world.

On the road since 2017

Fullstack Web Developer (React + Node) Mobile (React Native)

light UI / UX Designer

## Experience

Marknadsinformation i Sverige AB
Fullstack Web Developer
November 2018 - Present (2 years 8 months)
Stockholm. Sweden

Marknadsinformation provides information, addresses and phone numbers, of all private persons/households and companies in Sweden.

Duties: Building from scratch or modernizing existing applications within the company.

- Front: React.js & Friends

- Back: Node.js

I also contribute to UX, architectural decisions and overall integrity of the applications.

We are market leading provider of tools for selections, cleansing and analysis software.

Through own performed interviews we deliver the best coverage of named decision makers, e-mail addresses and direct phone numbers.

Website: http://www.marknadsinformation.se/

### Upwork

Freelance Web Developer (React / Node) July 2017 - January 2021 (3 years 7 months) Serbia

Working on large projects (developing standalone applications, TDD components) as well as small projects (React-related upgrades, bug fixes, feature implementations).

My stack of choice for building applications includes React + Next + Redux, Node, CSS-in-JS, and Webpack/Babel, but I still develop in VanillaJS per clients need.

TO HIRE: https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~016ed50347a6c22eb6

CallidusCloud Frontend Web Developer May 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 5 months) Serbia

\*\* ACQUIRED BY SAP \*\*

Actively working on developing Clicktools (a product of CallidusCloud).

#### Duties include:

- User Interface (React)
- Server & API (Node)
- Mockups and Prototypes
- ... anything Web related

More info: http://www.clicktools.com/

Computer Rock Frontend Developer December 2017 - May 2018 (6 months) Belgrade, Serbia

Typical day:

- Building frontend components

- UX/UI and responsiveness

- Optimizing code for better performance

Current project: https://stilwerk.com/

Stack:

Language: Javascript (ES5 & ES6), HTML5, CSS3

Framework/Library: React, Redux, jQuery, SASS, Twig, MaterializeCSS,

**Bootstrap** 

Code Versioning: Git

Package Manager: Yarn, npm

Module Loader: Webpack, gulp, RequireJS

Testing: Mocha + Chai

Limited knowledge of: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB

Bringsy Inc.

**Account Manager** 

December 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Bringsy (http://bringsy.com) is a same day rush delivery service that connects businesses to our network of already existing professional courier companies with software and logistics intelligence.

Entrepreneur Handbook Key Account Manager June 2015 - December 2015 (7 months)

Limassol, Cyprus

Broker scouts, analyses and connects you with startups based entirely on your needs. Whether you're looking to on-board growth stage clients in a specific vertical or for qualified investment opportunities, we can help by finding the right companies for you.

We use leading data and AI technology, a global network of scouts and our expert team to access and connect with millions of new and growing companies across the world.

# Education

Belgrade Institute of Technology

Javascript Developer, Frontend Web Development, Computer Science · (2017 - 2017)

University of Belgrade

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2011 - 2021)